(Penny:)Oh, you are such a--
[BLENDER WHIRRING]
(Penny:)-What the hell is he doing?
-Drowning us out. He doesn't like fighting.
(Penny:)Sheldon, just stop.
Look, the fight is over.
(Penny:)Oh, and FYI. You never even heard
of the Black Eyed Peas...
(Penny:)...until you met me.
I heard of them.
I didn't know they were a band.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, she's gone.
You can turn off the blender.
[BLENDER STOPS]
(Sheldon:)Has your relationship reached
its inevitable ugly end?
(Leonard:)No, we just had a little spat.
(Sheldon:)Look on the bright side.
As a result of Penny's forfeit...
(Sheldon:)...you have become
the world's first winner of Research Lab.
(Sheldon:)Would you like a commemorative
snow cone?